<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>retrovision on Beercave Games - putting the fun back into functional alcoholism!</title>
    <link>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/tags/retrovision/</link>
    <description>Recent content in retrovision on Beercave Games - putting the fun back into functional alcoholism!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 21:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/tags/retrovision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Well, that was an eventful weekend</title>
      <link>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/blog/2014/04/09/rom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/blog/2014/04/09/rom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was when I careered into the pub car park in a vehicle with no brakes for the second time in one day that I knew it was going to be a good weekend. The Beermobile had thoughtfully held it together for the preceding 200 miles or so before finally deciding to dump hydraulic fluid all over the road about half a mile from my final destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not the most auspicious of starts to the ROM retro gaming festival, but it could only get better from there&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On a Mission (Retromission 2013)</title>
      <link>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/blog/2013/09/25/mission-retromission-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 21:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/blog/2013/09/25/mission-retromission-2013/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This weekend I took a break from swearing at Java to head on down to Oxford for the first &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.retromission.co.uk/&#34;&gt;Retromission&lt;/a&gt; event. Rising from the ashes of the now sadly defunct Retrovision, we had a new name, a newly-
renamed pub, and more-or-less the same crowd of drinkers and gamers as usual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being an easily-led numpty, I&amp;rsquo;d let myself be talked into running one of the gaming competitions, and thus &amp;ldquo;Beerman&amp;rsquo;s Beercade Homebrew Challenge&amp;rdquo; was born! A high score tournament across four top notch homebrew games made by event and associated forum regulars. With a flash of last-minute inspiration leading to having a homebrew beer kit as the prize, it turned out pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;display:block; margin-left:auto; margin-right:auto;&#34; src=&#34;https://s3.amazonaws.com/beercave.co.uk/blogpics/beercadeposter.png&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Games&lt;h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://ncot.piku.org.uk/ncot-p-007-dotshooter/&#34;&gt;DotShooter&lt;/a&gt; (NCOT Software)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tcksoft.co.uk/wordpress/downloads/remakes/pangic-plus/&#34;&gt;PANgIC PLUS&lt;/a&gt; (TCKSoft)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.alexarisgames.co.uk/dpi.htm&#34;&gt;Dead Pixel Invaders&lt;/a&gt; (Alex Aris Games)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.beercave.co.uk/games/junohunter-prologue&#34;&gt;Juno Hunter&lt;/a&gt; (Some cowboy outfit called Beercave or something)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All-in-all the competition was a great success, and I&amp;rsquo;ll definitely be up for organising a repeat at next year&amp;rsquo;s event. With a bit of luck, it&amp;rsquo;s inspired a few of the regulars to take a crack at making their own games as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>