<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recap on Beercave Games - putting the fun back into functional alcoholism!</title>
    <link>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/tags/recap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recap on Beercave Games - putting the fun back into functional alcoholism!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 02:47:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/tags/recap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2013 : So long and thanks for all the games</title>
      <link>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/blog/2013/12/31/2013-so-long-and-thanks-all-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 02:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/blog/2013/12/31/2013-so-long-and-thanks-all-games/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, that about wraps it up for 2013. It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit of a busy one, so this might take a while&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_Previously on &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s Beerman been up to this year&amp;rdquo; : _&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/2013/01/07/2012-was-fun&#34;&gt;2012&lt;/a&gt;
,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/2012/01/01/post-mortem-2011&#34;&gt;2011&lt;/a&gt;
,
&lt;a href=&#34;https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/2010/12/31/2010-and-all&#34;&gt;2010&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work-wise, things have been a tad more stable. I&amp;rsquo;m considerably happier with the less corporate-bullshitty/cult-of-personality environment of the new gig, despite occasional forays into the Hell that is Sharepoint. My God, someone needs hurting for that thing&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not that you guys care - if anyone&amp;rsquo;s genuinely coming here to read about the ins and outs of my day job I&amp;rsquo;m frankly a bit worried about them. So, on to the games!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, as you may have noticed (I mentioned it once or twice, I&amp;rsquo;m sure), back at the end of 2012 I managed to talk myself into signing up for &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/mcfunkypants&#34;&gt;@McFunkyPants&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.onegameamonth.com/&#34;&gt;One Game a Month&lt;/a&gt; initiative. And damn, it&amp;rsquo;s been quite a ride.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2012 : That was... fun?</title>
      <link>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/blog/2013/01/07/2012-was-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 22:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/blog/2013/01/07/2012-was-fun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s that time again, where I take a look back at the events of the last year and ask the question : what the hell was all that about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previous installments : &lt;a href=&#34;https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/2012/01/01/post-mortem-2011&#34;&gt;2011&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://technicalhat.github.io/beercave-web/2010/12/31/2010-and-all&#34;&gt;2010&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, my plans for the year ganged pretty damn agly but everything pretty much worked itself out in the end. Seems I just don&amp;rsquo;t have the required hustle for contracting - after 6 months on the bench my cash reserves were pretty much all gone, Mrs Beerman was beginning to get a little impatient with bankrolling me, and our conveniently-timed rent-free house/cat sitting deal was fixing to expire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the game development front, Playing Gods was sadly cancelled and Droidy Shooty Thing was an engine looking for a game. The outlook was bleak for our Hero.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>